

# **ADOOLWIT BOOTPO**

### อดูลวิทย์ บุตรโพธิ์

48 m.6, Huai sai, Nongkae, Saraburi 18230

6 08 7760 6849

adoolwit.bootpo@gmail.com

4 nadesh52.github.io

#### **SUMMARY**

A data-driven with passion. Experience in Video Games, Esport and competitive games over 10 years. Self-taught and practiced as a front-end web developer, specializing in HTML, JavaScript using the React.js library and the Next.js framework.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing Collaborator, Esports executive

Jan 2020 - Aug 2020

**VNG** Corporation

- Live stream online game tournament
- Organize online tournament
- Statistic summarize

Game Content writer

2013 - 2014

#### Compgamer News (TGPL)

- Online content writer
- Live stream online and offline game tournament
- Organize online and lan tournament

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Fine and Applied art (Digital art)

2015 - 2019

Sripatum University

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATIONS

Programing Language: HTML, CSS, Javascript, TypeScript, SQL Frameworks/Libraries: ReactJs, Next.Js, Tailwind CSS, ExpressJS

Coding Skills: Version Control (Git)

Interpersonal Skills: Good Listener, Good Follower

Certifications: Google Data Analytics, freeCodeCamp (Responsive Web Design)

Language: Thai (Native), English (Basic)